Guide to the North Side Laundry Company, Pittsburgh, Pa. Records, 1877-1943 AIS.1966.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
North Side Laundry Company, Pittsburgh, Pa. Records
1877-1943
ULS Archives & Special Collections
North Side Laundry Company
AIS.1966.02
1.25 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
This collection contains stockholder and board of director's meeting minutes, mortgages, deeds, bonds, and lease records for the North Side Laundry Company of Pittsburgh, Pa., for the years 1877-1943.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains stockholder and board of director's meeting minutes, mortgages, deeds, bonds, and lease records for the North Side Laundry Company of Allegheny City, Pa. (now Pittsburgh's North Side) for the years 1877-1943. The records are arranged chronologically by subject.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Paul Davis, January 12, 1966.
Previous Citation
North Side Laundry Company, Pittsburgh, Pa. Records, 1877-1943, AIS.1966.02, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
North Laundry Business Papers, 1877-1943, AIS 66:2, Archives of Industrial Society, University Library System, University of Pittsburgh
North Side (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Laundry industry -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Laundry industry -- Pennsylvania -- Allegheny; Business and Industry; North Side Laundry Company
- Stockholders Meeting Minutes, 1907; I.
  - Organization Meeting of Stockholders Minutes, September 24, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - First Meeting of Stockholders, November 1, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Minutes of Director's Meetings, 1910-1955; II.
  - November 18, 1910-December 24, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - February 16, 1911-December 7, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - January 7, 1915-December 7, 1915 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - January 7, 1916-January 8, 1918 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - January 29, 1918-February 9, 1920 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - February 23, 1920-June 8, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - July 9, 1921-February 21, 1923 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - March 7, 1923-December 8, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - January 8, 1925-December 8, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - January 7, 1927-December 7, 1928 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1929-1932 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - January 9, 1933-December 7, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - January 8, 1935-December 8, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - January 8, 1937-December 8, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - January 8, 1938-December 7, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - January 9, 1939-December 8, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - January 8, 1940-December 8, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - January 8, 1942-December 9, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - January 7, 1944-December 8, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - January 8, 1946-December 9, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - January 9, 1948-December 9, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - January 9, 1950-September 7, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - October 9, 1951-November 9, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - December 9, 1953-September 8, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Legal Material, 1877-1948; III.
  - Bond, Insurance, and Lease Records, 1894-1929 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Mortgages, 1894-1927 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Deeds, 1877-1894 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Deeds, 1907-1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Legal Brief - Property Assessment Appeal, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 14)